{
    "id": "b3e987f4a1c6453eb906ba7e7c52a27d",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Delhi is …………….. than Mumbai.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hot",
                "hotter",
                "hottest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………….. youngest brother serves in the army.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "My",
                "Me",
                "Mine"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We had ………………. most interesting experience during the picnic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Mr. Ramesh is ……………….. most popular lecturer in our college.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am satisfied only with ………………… best.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Kodaikanal is one of the ……………… hill stations in South India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lovely",
                "lovelier",
                "loveliest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………… of the two brothers is getting married next month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "younger",
                "youngest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ……………….. most useful book on the subject.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have not seen ………………… better film than this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Only the ………………. member can be elected the President.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "old",
                "older",
                "oldest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ……………….. worst accident in recent times.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. Charles seemed to be covered with hair.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most of",
                "The most of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}